scared...
怖い...
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
Sorry, suddenly...
ごめんね、急に...
I turned the camera...
カメラ回しちゃって...
Just a hobby
ちょっと趣味で
...
You look scared...
怯 えてるね...
Don't be scared...
怯えないで...
Because it's okay...
大丈夫だから...
Because I haven't done anything like this...
こういうことしてないから...
Can I ask you a few questions?
ちょっといろいろ聞いてもいい?
How old are you now?
今何歳ある?
4 years old...
4歳...
I'm back to school...
学校帰ってんだ...
How old are you?
何年生?
Why me?
俺なんで?
Examination?
受験?
I'm studying for the exam...
受験勉強じゃん...
very soon...
もうすぐ...
What kind of story?
どんな話?
Is it okay?
いいの?
Have you decided?
決めてるの?
University...
大学...
Suddenly...
急にね...
You're surprised...
びっくりしてるね...
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
This is for hobby...
これ趣味用なんで...
University?
大学?
I'm studying...
勉強してるんだ...
What do you want to study?
何を勉強したい?
I'm thinking about it
とか考えてる
...
Department of Science?
理 系?
Humanities?
文系?
Humanities...
文系...
It's on the uniform...
制服にはね...
copper?
どう?
this...
これ...
I brought it...
俺が持ってきたんですよ...
How about regular uniforms?
普段の制服とどう?
Are they similar?
似 てる?
same?
同じ?
Does it feel the same?
同じ感じ?
Check?
チェックの?
Is it a blazer?
ブレザーフだ?
What about socks?
靴下は?
These are the socks...
靴下はこういうの...
Is it like this?
こういうのか
...
Do you have a part-time job?
バイ トとかしてるの?
How are you doing?
どうしてるの?
A part-time job like this?
こういうバイト?
This isn't a part-time job...ordinary part-time job?
こういうバイトじゃないよ...普通のバイト?
Do you have a part-time job like this?
こういうバイトはしてるの?
I haven't...
してない...
Haven't you?
してない?
Don't make any noise
音しちゃダメだよ
...
Do you have a boyfriend?
彼 氏いんの?
Are you there?
いる?
Is there someone you like?
好きな人いる?
boyfriend...
彼氏...
Do you have that kind of edgy sound with your boyfriend?
彼氏とそういうエッジな音してる?
Good...youth...
いい...青春だね...
Youth...or should I say youth...
青春...青春っていうか...
Same school...with my boyfriend
同じ学校...彼氏と
...
No nuisance...
迷 惑力もない...
What?
なんの?
boyfriend...
彼氏...
See you...
じゃあね...
Chew...
チ ュ ーして...
Ask me to chew...
チューしてもらって...
Isn't it fun?
楽しいでしょ?
What should I do?
どうするの?
you
お前
...
Because you don't say chu...
チ ューって言わないから...
Please let me down a little...
ちょっと下出してもらって...
Even if you lower it a little...
ちょっと 下 出 して も ら って...
I was surprised...
びっくりした...
Were you surprised?
びっくりしたの?
Have you ever had a chew like this?
まさかこういうチューしたことない?
Isn't there?
ないの?
This is how you do it...
こうやるんだよ...
I'll tell you...
教えてあげるから...
This is bab...
これバブ...
Isn't this Baba?
これバブでしょ?
that...
それ...
Wait a minute...that's Babu...
ちょっと待って...それバブだって...
No...I need you to lower me...
違う...下出してもらって...
Bottom... are you going to take out the bottom?
下...下を出すの?
Ah, yes, yes...
あ、そうそうそう...
What about bub?
バブは?
Oh, that's Babu!
あ、それバブだ!
this...
これ...
Babu... It's not Babu...
バブ...バブじゃないから...
Take out the bottom... and connect it like this...
下を出して...こう絡める...
Why... why...
なんでしょ...なんで...
Why is that...why is that...
なんでそう...なんでそんな...
It's intertwined...
絡めるのさ...
Hey...hey...hey...
ちょ...ちょ...ちょっと...
I'm disappointed... What happened to this?
やっかりした...これどうしたの?
How was it?
どうでしたの?
Why don't you be nice...really?
いいやつしてねえかよ...本当に
hey...
ね...
What is this?
なにこれ?
Have you thought about hedging?
ヘッジなこと考えた?
Wow...what is this?
すげえ...なにこれ?
What did you check?
なにを確認したの?
Wait... that's amazing...
ちょ ... すごい...
What is this?
これなに?
underwear...
下着...
Skew...
ス ケスケ...
Isn't it too sexy?
スケすぎじゃない?
this...
これ...
You can see this...
見えてるじゃん...これ...
Eh...when...will we go on like this?
え...いつの間...こう...これでいくの?
Is it going to turn out like this?
こういうのになっていくの?
Seriously?
マジで?
Kids these days are terrible...
最近の子やばい...
I took my own camera...sorry.
自分でカメラ...ごめん
...
Is the scale...already...finished?
ス ケ...もう...終われてるの?
here
ここ
...
What's going on?
一 応どうなってるでしょ?
touch it
触ってごらん
Well...
じゃ ん...
Why barbutan?
なんでバーブタンするの?
that...
それ...
Just in case...just in case...just in case...
一応...一応...一応...
I haven't been throwing up all day today.
今日一日吐いてたじゃないもんね
...
Then...
そ したらその...
I have long legs...
足長い足です...
This can't come off, can it?
これ外れないんじゃない?
Maybe
もしかして
...
Ah...it won't come off...
あ...外れない...
I can't leave here...
ここ...ここ外れないんだ...
fault...
あら...
Oh no...oh no
やべえ...やべ
picture...
え...
Oh no...
やべえ...
Why is it so bad?
なんでやべえの?
It's a bit of a feeling
ちょっと感じのさ
...
No...you have a great type.
いや...すっごいタイプ出してるね
...
Oh... amazing... what is that...
おお...すごい...なにそれ...
yeah?
ん?
Will you do it?
やってくれるの?
Like this...
こんな...
After all this time...it's amazing
こんな時間これ終わって...すごいね
...
I can't stand it...
我 慢できない...
What should I do...
どうしよう...
Can I give you anything?
何も出して...いい?
Just like this...
このまま...
Nothing is coming out...
何も出してる...
I haven't released it...
出してないもん...
I haven't put it out at all...
全然出してない...